# 617.686.1147



## amyhwang1218@gmail.com



https://github.com/amy1hwang



https://www.linkedin.com/in/amy1hwang

in

Lunior Wah Davalanar specializaing in front and design and devalonment. Wall versed in Skatch ann ar

Junior Web Developer specializeing in front-end design and development. Well-versed in Sketch app and programming languages including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Experienced in pair programming and Test Driven Development.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Beginning with Children Charter School** — 2015 - 2016

AMY HWANG

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

### **Music Teacher**

- Created a long-term curriculum and daily lesson plans that meet national music education standards and students' needs.
- Recruited musically talented students and ran an afterschool band program to expand their abilities.
- Organized Winter concert and Spring concert where every student of the school performed using their voices and instruments.
- Cooperated with other teachers to infuse different subjects into music and executed the projects through monthly assemblies and concerts.

### Manhattan Korean School — 2013 - 2014

## **Communication Director**

- Interpreted and translated Korean documents to English, ensured the meaning of the source text were retained.
- Acted as a communication liaison between the board members of the school and the parents.
- Managed information such as school budget, directories, and students information using spread sheet.

### **EDUCATION**

**Epicodus** – 2016 - 2017

### **Design Track**

- Sketch
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Pair Programming

New York University - 2009 - 2013

B.M., Music Education

## SKILL & EXPERIENCE

## Program Language and App:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Liquid, Sketch

## Framework, Library:

SASS, Bootstrap, Bourbon, MaterializeCSS JQuery, Angular2, Ember

#### **Other Skills:**

Shopify, TDD, Git, Pair Programming

#### Language:

Korean - Native or bilingual proficiency

#### **PROJECT**

### **Spread On Me**

## https://amy1hwang.github.io/spread-on-me

Spread On Me is a mock-up website for Claire Cook who is starting a flavored butter brand.

For the website, HTML, CSS, SASS, Bourbon, Javascript, and JQuery were used.

### **Arctic Wild**

#### https://amy1hwang.github.io/arctic-wild/

Arctic Wild was developed as one of the weekly independent projects. The project was to replicate at the top part of the actually website of Arctic Wild (http://arcticwild.com/).

In the project, HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript, and JQuery were used.